(Penny:)Based on real events.
(Raj:)Anyway, I was hoping
I could, uh, pick your brains a little.
(Raj:)I'm supposed to take Lucy out Friday
and I need a killer first date.
(Amy:)Evolutionary biology
says that women are attracted to a man...
...who is steady in the face of danger,
so I recommend an unsafe environment.
A seedy bar
on the wrong side of the tracks...
...a picnic near a lunatic asylum...
...a wine-tasting on skid row.
(Raj:)Lucy has some, uh, social anxiety issues,
we could start with something simpler.
(Bernadette:)Why don't you take her to Disneyland?
(Bernadette:)You go on Space Mountain,
you're in the dark, she's holding onto you.
(Penny:)That ride is shorter than you think...
(Penny:)...and they take a picture of you at the end,
so make sure you got your clothes on.
It's ajoke.
(Penny:)Based on real events.
(Raj:)Disneyland? I don't know.
(Raj:)With all the crowds
and the weird characters walking around...